nextechclassifieds.com 2018-12-30

# Nex-Tech Classifieds

## Privacy Policy

This Agreement is between you and Nex-Tech, LLC, with corporate headquarters located at 145 North Main, Lenora, KS 67645, hereinafter referred to as "DiscoverStuff," This Privacy Policy describes DiscoverStuff's collection, use, disclosure, retention and protection of your personal information on our website and all related affiliate sites, tools, applications and services (collectively "Services"). By using DiscoverStuff's Services and/or registering for an account, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy and DiscoverStuff's User Agreement, and you are consenting to DiscoverStuff's collection, use, disclosure, retention and protection of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not provide the required information, DiscoverStuff may not be able to provide all of its Services to you. 

### Data Collection

You can browse the site anonymously without revealing any personal data. Once you sign up for an account, you are no longer anonymous to DiscoverStuff's employees or other users. By creating an account, you are providing consent to the storage and transfer of any related data to third parties as needed to provide services to you. 

#### **Potential Data Collected:**

  * Email address, phone numbers, address, username, password, IP address, location, usage and web log data. 
  * When communicating with other users, all messages sent or received via the DiscoverStuff site are stored and archived. 
  * Any data required to connect to third-party sites, e.g., Facebook, Twitter, etc. 
  * As a business account holder, credit card and billing information will be collected. 

### Use and Retention

DiscoverStuff uses the personal information collected to: provide and improve its Services, provide a personalized experience on DiscoverStuff's Services (e.g., offering services and items you may like), contact you about your account and Services, provide customer service, provide personalized advertising and marketing, and detect, prevent, mitigate and investigate fraudulent or illegal activities. 

DiscoverStuff retains your personal information as long as it is necessary and relevant for its operations. In addition, DiscoverStuff may retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with national laws, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigation, enforce DiscoverStuff's User Agreement and take other actions permitted or required by applicable national laws. 

### Security

DiscoverStuff will use reasonable best efforts to protect your information using technical and administrative security measures to reduce the risk of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration. Some of the safeguards used are firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls to DiscoverStuff's data centers and information access authorization controls. If you believe your account has been abused, please contact DiscoverStuff following the instructions in the Contact Us section below. 

### Marketing Data

DiscoverStuff does not provide or sell private user data to any third parties for any reason. DiscoverStuff reserves the right to anonymize data for statistical reporting. 

DiscoverStuff uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the DiscoverStuff website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice, or to learn about your options for opting out from having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

### Third Party Sites

DiscoverStuff may offer single sign-on services that allow you to use third-party login credentials to sign into the site. With your permission, DiscoverStuff may also transfer profile information contained in your third-party profile. Additionally, DiscoverStuff may, for your use, enable you to import information about who you are connected to, as well as enable you to share information with those third-party sites. If you wish to discontinue such sharing, you will be able to do so through your My Account area. 

### Information Disclosure

DiscoverStuff may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce DiscoverStuff policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. 

### Changes

DiscoverStuff's Privacy Policy may be amended at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms take place automatically. DiscoverStuff will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page. 

### Contact Us

By Email at [info@discoverstuff.com](mailto:info@discoverstuff.com)

By Phone at 877-344-2037

Last updated 04/30/2018 – JN
